Janine and I are at the store.
For what ?  Uh, because we're going to a
hotel.  So, we're at Decathlon
to get a swimsuit.  Because I don't have any
.  I decided I was going to run away from home
.   First
, we arrive in the
shower.  At the small shower.  Perfect.
That's more than enough.  The little pee-
poo.  Next, we arrive in the room
where we are going to sleep.  It's very cute,
I love it.  It's very warming, let's
say.  Obviously, the TV, there, we have
the outside, it's very pretty.  Okay,
Janine, what's up?  What are you doing on the
floor there?  Janine, she
absolutely wants to try out the swimming pool.  Shall we go to the
swimming pool?  OK.
Janine is definitely there.  Was the
swimming pool nice?  No, it was great.
She was really hot.
What are you going to get us to
eat?
That's it, we're finally in bed.  We're going to have
a long sleep.  Ingen Yeah.  Don't
hit me in the night.  Yes.  Ben does
n't see a hit.  So.  Come on, come on,
kisses.  What do we say?  Okay,
kisses to the little ones.